<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal story on Alayna, Mary, Kim</title>
    <link>/tags/personal-story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal story on Alayna, Mary, Kim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/personal-story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneur paves the way in male-dominated tech industry</title>
      <link>/posts/roya-ansari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roya-ansari/</guid>
      <description>Through innovative thinking, hard work and principled determination, Iranian-American Roya Ansari has led a successful career in Silicon Valley, marked by the founding of her own data companies and a generous commitment to paying it forward. This is Roya&amp;rsquo;s story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant Goes Against the Status Quo</title>
      <link>/posts/anne-kue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anne-kue/</guid>
      <description>Anne Kue&amp;rsquo;s parents were Hmong refugees that came to the U.S. in the 1990s. Due to the large influx of Hmong refugees at the time, they were forced to relocate again and again until they found the perfect home in the suburbs of Minnesota. As a first-generation immigrant, Anne faced many challenges growing up, but those obstacles did not discourage her, instead they inspired her to embrace her uniqueness and her passion to help underserved populations. Want to hear more about her journey? Read more to find out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Cambodian turned American researcher</title>
      <link>/posts/bunchung-ly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bunchung-ly/</guid>
      <description>As a teenager, Bunchung left Cambodia on his own to pursue his dreams of earning a higher-quality education abroad. After a rigorous selection process, Bunchung won a full scholarship to study International Baccalaureate in Singapore. Two years later, he again received full financial aid to pursue his B.A. degree at Macalester College in St Paul, MN. As a first-generation college student, he faced many hurdles. They did not stop him, but pushed him to work harder towards his goals. Continue reading for his full story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From a refugee in Kenya to an A&#43; student in the U.S.</title>
      <link>/posts/umar-hassan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/umar-hassan/</guid>
      <description>Immigrating to the U.S. at a young age with little English, Umar faced many challenges, from having to make himself feel at home in an absolutely foreign place to confronting his principal in order to receive the education that he deserved. These obstacles did not hold Umar back. Umar adapted, persisted, and rose to the occasion. How did he do it? Continue reading to find out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>