<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Izzy’s Ice Cream came to be an Iconic Twin Cities company</title>
      <link>/posts/jess-sommers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/jess-sommers/</guid>
      <description>He has been an English major, an art graduate student and a teacher. Now, he is the owner of Izzy’s Ice Cream, one of the most iconic Twin Cities companies. Jeff Sommers knows something about winding roads, taking risks and fearlessly changing career paths. Jeff and his wife Lara took two mortgages and a $280,000 investment and transformed it into a thriving business with two locations and hundreds of grocery and restaurant distributors, an iconic Twin Cities brand and a gathering place for their community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A with Rachel Dungca: on fearlessly evolving your career</title>
      <link>/posts/rachel-dungca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rachel-dungca/</guid>
      <description>Rachel Dungca is no stranger to change and evolution. In both her professional and personal life, Rachel has worn numerous hats. From German major to a strategic communications master’s degree graduate. From young professional to wife to mother of two. From MetroTransit Marketing Specialist to Revenue Operations Specialist to Performance Manager. These evolutions did not just happen to Rachel. Through hard work, confidence and intentionality, Rachel worked to build and seize these opportunities. AMK sat down with Rachel to find out more about her story and how we can all confidently take actions to achieve our professional and personal goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An accounting manager on getting the career you want</title>
      <link>/posts/ian-petersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ian-petersen/</guid>
      <description>Always with a goal in mind, Ian Petersen worked his way through his Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and Master&amp;rsquo;s in Business Administration degrees while working full-time, and ended up in a career he wanted. Through this journey, he has learned many valuable lessons. Read Ian&amp;rsquo;s story to see how he got to where he is today and to gain great insights into how you can break into today&amp;rsquo;s job market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneur paves the way in male-dominated tech industry</title>
      <link>/posts/roya-ansari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roya-ansari/</guid>
      <description>Through innovative thinking, hard work and principled determination, Iranian-American Roya Ansari has led a successful career in Silicon Valley, marked by the founding of her own data companies and a generous commitment to paying it forward. This is Roya&amp;rsquo;s story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant Goes Against the Status Quo</title>
      <link>/posts/anne-kue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anne-kue/</guid>
      <description>Anne Kue&amp;rsquo;s parents were Hmong refugees that came to the U.S. in the 1990s. Due to the large influx of Hmong refugees at the time, they were forced to relocate again and again until they found the perfect home in the suburbs of Minnesota. As a first-generation immigrant, Anne faced many challenges growing up, but those obstacles did not discourage her, instead they inspired her to embrace her uniqueness and her passion to help underserved populations. Want to hear more about her journey? Read more to find out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Cambodian turned American researcher</title>
      <link>/posts/bunchung-ly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bunchung-ly/</guid>
      <description>As a teenager, Bunchung left Cambodia on his own to pursue his dreams of earning a higher-quality education abroad. After a rigorous selection process, Bunchung won a full scholarship to study International Baccalaureate in Singapore. Two years later, he again received full financial aid to pursue his B.A. degree at Macalester College in St Paul, MN. As a first-generation college student, he faced many hurdles. They did not stop him, but pushed him to work harder towards his goals. Continue reading for his full story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From a refugee in Kenya to an A&#43; student in the U.S.</title>
      <link>/posts/umar-hassan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/umar-hassan/</guid>
      <description>Immigrating to the U.S. at a young age with little English, Umar faced many challenges, from having to make himself feel at home in an absolutely foreign place to confronting his principal in order to receive the education that he deserved. These obstacles did not hold Umar back. Umar adapted, persisted, and rose to the occasion. How did he do it? Continue reading to find out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who we are</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>We are Alayna Hoy, Mary Fisher, and Kim Eng Ky. We created this blog to share inspirational stories of people who have achieved success, even in the face of many obstacles. We hope to inform, motivate and encourage our readers to live their dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>