<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>career advice on </title>
    <link>/tags/career-advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in career advice on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/career-advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A with Rachel Dungca: on fearlessly evolving your career</title>
      <link>/posts/rachel-dungca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rachel-dungca/</guid>
      <description>Rachel Dungca is no stranger to change and evolution. In both her professional and personal life, Rachel has worn numerous hats. From German major to a strategic communications master’s degree graduate. From young professional to wife to mother of two. From MetroTransit Marketing Specialist to Revenue Operations Specialist to Performance Manager. These evolutions did not just happen to Rachel. Through hard work, confidence and intentionality, Rachel worked to build and seize these opportunities. AMK sat down with Rachel to find out more about her story and how we can all confidently take actions to achieve our professional and personal goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An accounting manager on getting the career you want</title>
      <link>/posts/ian-petersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ian-petersen/</guid>
      <description>Always with a goal in mind, Ian Petersen worked his way through his Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and Master&amp;rsquo;s in Business Administration degrees while working full-time, and ended up in a career he wanted. Through this journey, he has learned many valuable lessons. Read Ian&amp;rsquo;s story to see how he got to where he is today and to gain great insights into how you can break into today&amp;rsquo;s job market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>