<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rebellion on </title>
    <link>/tags/rebellion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rebellion on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/rebellion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A with Rachel Dungca: on fearlessly evolving your career</title>
      <link>/posts/rachel-dungca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rachel-dungca/</guid>
      <description>Rachel Dungca is no stranger to change and evolution. In both her professional and personal life, Rachel has worn numerous hats. From German major to a strategic communications master’s degree graduate. From young professional to wife to mother of two. From MetroTransit Marketing Specialist to Revenue Operations Specialist to Performance Manager. These evolutions did not just happen to Rachel. Through hard work, confidence and intentionality, Rachel worked to build and seize these opportunities. AMK sat down with Rachel to find out more about her story and how we can all confidently take actions to achieve our professional and personal goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant Goes Against the Status Quo</title>
      <link>/posts/anne-kue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anne-kue/</guid>
      <description>Anne Kue&amp;rsquo;s parents were Hmong refugees that came to the U.S. in the 1990s. Due to the large influx of Hmong refugees at the time, they were forced to relocate again and again until they found the perfect home in the suburbs of Minnesota. As a first-generation immigrant, Anne faced many challenges growing up, but those obstacles did not discourage her, instead they inspired her to embrace her uniqueness and her passion to help underserved populations. Want to hear more about her journey? Read more to find out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From a refugee in Kenya to an A&#43; student in the U.S.</title>
      <link>/posts/umar-hassan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/umar-hassan/</guid>
      <description>Immigrating to the U.S. at a young age with little English, Umar faced many challenges, from having to make himself feel at home in an absolutely foreign place to confronting his principal in order to receive the education that he deserved. These obstacles did not hold Umar back. Umar adapted, persisted, and rose to the occasion. How did he do it? Continue reading to find out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>