<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>resilience on Alayna, Mary, Kim</title>
    <link>/tags/resilience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in resilience on Alayna, Mary, Kim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/resilience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An accounting manager on getting the career you want</title>
      <link>/posts/ian-petersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ian-petersen/</guid>
      <description>Always with a goal in mind, Ian Petersen worked his way through his Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and Master&amp;rsquo;s in Business Administration degrees while working full-time, and ended up in a career he wanted. Through this journey, he has learned many valuable lessons. Read Ian&amp;rsquo;s story to see how he got to where he is today and to gain great insights into how you can break into today&amp;rsquo;s job market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneur paves the way in male-dominated tech industry</title>
      <link>/posts/roya-ansari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roya-ansari/</guid>
      <description>Through innovative thinking, hard work and principled determination, Iranian-American Roya Ansari has led a successful career in Silicon Valley, marked by the founding of her own data companies and a generous commitment to paying it forward. This is Roya&amp;rsquo;s story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Cambodian turned American researcher</title>
      <link>/posts/bunchung-ly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bunchung-ly/</guid>
      <description>As a teenager, Bunchung left Cambodia on his own to pursue his dreams of earning a higher-quality education abroad. After a rigorous selection process, Bunchung won a full scholarship to study International Baccalaureate in Singapore. Two years later, he again received full financial aid to pursue his B.A. degree at Macalester College in St Paul, MN. As a first-generation college student, he faced many hurdles. They did not stop him, but pushed him to work harder towards his goals. Continue reading for his full story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>